

Mohsinahmed Saiyad

Phone: +91 97122 46825

Address: 302, Sumin Residency,

Sarani Road, Opp. Khaibar Masjid,

Juhapura,

Ahmedabad-380055

Birth Date: 01/07/1989

Email: mohsin.saiyad@outlook.com

I am an approachable, motivated and confident Business Manager with the ability to excel sales targets and make a real difference in the organization's revenue generation.

I have expert knowledge of the selling process and I fully recognize the human and emotional aspects of buying and selling. I possess strong social skills that enable me to be a strong relationship builder with clients, colleagues and third-party stakeholders.

EXPERIENCE

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited

January 2021 - Present

Associate Business Manager - Business Development Manager

- Primary responsibility will be training & stimulating team of advisors to generate business.
- The advisor performs the role of suspecting, prospecting & referencing to acquire new customers.
- Generating new customer leads and building a robust pipeline for business generation.
- Explaining the various type of products like ULIPS, Endowment, pure life and Health to Agents and Customers, and various other coordination required with Operations, HR and Other departments of the Company for streamlining of process within your team.
- Once the above conditions are met like training, customer meetings, development of List of customers then coming into action mode of driving business by selling of policies to customers and revenue generation.
- · Achieve sales targets through advisors. Handling and managing customers and team members.

Unicorn Info Solutions Pvt. Ltd.

October 2015 - January - 2021

Sales Executive

- Meeting with walk in clients.
- Identify their needs and values by asking effective questions.
- As per their needs and values demonstrating and presenting products.
- Establishing new business.
- Maintaining accurate records.
- Reviewing sales performance.
- Working towards monthly or annual targets.

HP (Xylem India Pvt. Ltd.)

April 2014 - April 2015

Tablet Consultant

- Meeting with walk in clients.
- Identify their needs and values by asking effective questions.
- As per their needs and values demonstrating and presenting products.
- · Establishing new business.
- · Maintaining accurate records.
- Reviewing sales performance.
- Working towards monthly or annual targets.

Samsung Mobile

November 2013 - April 2014

Sales Consultant

- Meeting with walk in clients.
- Identify their needs and values by asking effective questions.
- As per their needs and values demonstrating and presenting products.
- Establishing new business.

- Maintaining accurate records.
- Reviewing sales performance.
- Working towards monthly or annual targets.

Vodafone Store (Dhwani Marketing)

Data Champ

- Meeting with walk in clients.
- Identify their needs and values by asking effective questions.
- As per their needs Suggest them Data Plan.
- Also Taking Complain of Network issues and forwarded them to Network Team Personally.
- Maintaining accurate records.
- Reviewing sales performance.
- Working towards monthly or annual targets.

Vodafone BPO (Magus Customer Dialog Private Limited)

January 2008 - October 2010

January 2012 - November 2013

Customer Service Associate

- Respond to customer queries in a timely and accurate way, via phone.
- Identify customer needs and help customers use specific features.
- Update our internal databases with information about technical issues and useful discussions with customers.

EDUCATION

Monad University

June 2010 - May 2013

Bachelor of Arts

SKILLS

- Ability to Work in a Team
- Customer Service
- Communication Skills
- Building Rapport
- Building Relationships

LANGUAGES

English (Native), Hindi (Native), Gujarati (Native)

HOBBIES

Travelling, Sports, Movie, Creating and Maintaining Relationship

DECLARATION

I Mohsinahmed Saiyad hereby declare that the information contained here in is true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Your	Faithfully,

Mohsinahmed Saiyad